(Sheldon:)Penny?
(Howard:)Would you have opened the door
if you knew it was me?
(Penny:)Not since I found out
(Penny:)the teddy bear you gave me
had a webcam in it.
(Howard:)I just have a question.
(Howard:)Does Bernadette
ever talk about me?
(Penny:)Oh, absolutely.
(Howard:)She does?
Yeah, sure.
(Penny:)Just yesterday, she asked,
"Why is Howard hiding
under the table?"
(Howard:)She saw that, huh?
(Penny:)Oh, no, not at first.
(Penny:)Right after I pointed it out.
(Howard:)Let me ask you something else.
(Howard:)Is she seeing anybody?
Oh, not that I know of.
(Penny:)Hey, while
we're on the subject,
(Penny:)why did you guys break up
anyway?
(Howard:)Oh, I'd rather not say.
(Penny:)Howard, if you want my help,
I've got to know what happened.
(Howard:)But it's embarrassing...
(Penny:)Yeah, that's what
I'm counting on. Spill.
Okay. Well, you know
World of Warcraft?
(Penny:)Um, the online game? Sure.
(Howard:)Well, did you know
(Howard:)that the characters in the game
can have sex with each other?